https://www.stockgumshoe.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Overview
Stock Gumshoe takes data security and your personal privacy seriously. We take reasonable measures to secure your data. Email addresses, physical addresses, IP addresses, or other personally identifiable information will not be shared by Stock Gumshoe except in the course of necessary business, such as processing payment or sending our email newsletters to you. It may be disclosed as required by law or in response to legal processes, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Stock Gumshoe.
We collect information that you voluntarily give us via email, online forms, memberships, direct user engagement and commenting, and other direct contact from you. We also use third party statistics platforms and cookies to collect data in order to analyze aggregate user behavior and monitor content popularity. We will use your information to fulfill administrative tasks, enhance user experience, and rank content.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new content, your membership status, changes to this privacy policy, and other company news. You can unsubscribe from our emails at any time.
Our Goals
Stock Gumshoe respects users’ rights to their data. All data is secured to the best of our ability and most frequently used to enhance user experience and manage memberships. In broadest terms, we will use your information to make enhancements to the site and will not share any individually identifiable information with any third parties outside our organization.
Information We Collect
We may collect personally identifiable information about you such as your full name, email address, and site participation linked to your account. For our staff to fulfill paid functionality such as membership newsletters, there is some mandatory information that Stock Gumshoe will need to provide requested services. Information is most frequently gathered through our “Contact” and “Membership” forms, but may also be gathered from information provided in person or through customer support.
Your contributed content, including comments on articles, is more passively gathered on our content management system, WordPress. User behavior is collected from third party statistics providers, including but not limited to Google Analytics. Emails are predominately managed through Campaign Monitor.
How We Use Your Information
Personally identifiable information: We use data such as users’ email addresses for administrative purposes such as customer service, membership maintenance, newsletters, and notifications. Further, we use your data to track readership trends, analyze user preferences, improve service and web functionality, and highlight popular content.
Non-personally identifiable information: Stock Gumshoe may use statistics from the aggregate data of our users for promotional purposes.
Information Storage
Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Stock Gumshoe or its subsidiaries, affiliates, or service providers maintain facilities. Information is stored in our trusted host sites. We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Online: Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. We want to make sure that you’re protected and we strive to be transparent about all the data we may store on an individual.You can verify the site’s security by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
Offline: While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Information Protections
If you log in as a free or paid member on the site, an anonymous tracking number may be assigned to your behavior before and/or after logging in so that Stock Gumshoe can use Google Analytics to see which services or pages are most valuable to our members. That number is different than your member account number and site login and does not allow Google to individually identity you; however, your IP address could conceivably allow individual users to be identified. Your account information will be maintained in a separate database and is not sent to Google Analytics or other third party analysis partners.
Third Parties
Personally identifiable information: Stock Gumshoe will not share or sell identifiable information except in the course of necessary business. The course of business will include necessary tasks and partners. For example, our banks will use the address information you provide in the context of processing credit card payments. Information may also be disclosed as required by applicable law, response to legal processes, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Stock Gumshoe.
Data Breaches
A data breach is the unauthorized acquisition or use of sensitive personal information such as a Social Security Number, driver’s license number, and financial information, that creates a substantial risk of identity theft or fraud. In case of a serious data breach, Stock Gumshoe will notify all mandated supervisory authorities in accordance with Massachusetts state law.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. For email storage, Stock Gumshoe works in accordance with the privacy policy established by Campaign Monitor, which you can read here.
Mandatory Data
Different levels of membership may require different amounts of information in order to use this website and receive the services requested. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is primarily used to contact you about site content. All mandatory fields are marked on every online form and will be communicated when applicable in person. Unmarked fields, while not required, are helpful in pursuing your interests and improving your overall experience with Stock Gumshoe.
Cookies
We use “cookies” and marketing analytics tools on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can store information like your login credentials so that you can stay logged in. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance their experience on our site.
Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Further, in placing ads on Stock Gumshoe, third party advertising partners, including Google, may also place and read cookies on your browser or use web beacons to collect information. Google uses what they call a “DoubleClick DART” cookie to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet so they can show you advertisements related to your interests. You may specifically opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
User Rights
Some of the data rights for our clients and users include a right to be informed about how Stock Gumshoe is using your personal data, a right to access what information we have stored about you, a right to have your data rectified, and a right to object to how your data is being used.
Right To Be Forgotten
Some data may be omitted or stricken from our records upon user request, or removed from public view, but some may be retained for business operations and historic record. Names of readers who suggest story ideas or topics or forward newsletter ads will not be used without permission. Users can also request removal of their past comments on topics, though there is no guarantee that we can or will remove all traces of such comments. Publicly posted comments or posts by Stock Gumshoe readers are kept in perpetuity and remain publicly viewable unless the individual requests removal, and such requests will be considered on a case by case basis. Even if we remove individual comments or posts from our websites, they may still persist online in other forms (cached files of search engines, RSS feeds, etc.), and other users may have screenshots and records stored externally and outside of the control of Stock Gumshoe.
You Can
We respect your privacy rights and will provide reasonable access to the Personal Data that we have gathered. You can contact Stock Gumshoe at any time to:
request access to the information that Stock Gumshoe has about you
correct any information that Stock Gumshoe has on you
opt out of our email services
modify the amount of emails received.
Contact Information
If you have any additional questions about Stock Gumshoe’s data collection and storage of data, you can contact us through the online contact form or by fax, post, or phone.
Stock Gumshoe
351 Pleasant St.
Ste. B #205
Northampton, MA 01060
Fax: (866) 516-7341
Phone: (617) 249-4867 (toll free)
We use cookies on this site to enhance your user experience. By clicking any link on this page you are giving your consent for us to set cookies.
More Info  Arrow right
Ok, I Agree
